ADVAIT MANIT BISRAM

Full Stack Developer

St Julien D'Hotman | +230-5909-4340 | advait.bisram07.ab@gmail.com

Github | LinkedIn | Website

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer experienced in Python based programming with a background in Javascript, SQL, HTML and CSS. Possess strong skills in photo and video editing that helps in creating content for websites, companies and others as a freelancer.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- **Python**
 - Libraries : Numpy, Pandas • Frameworks : Django, Flask
 - OOP
- SQL
- **JavaScript**
 - DOM
- HTML
- CSS

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

MauBudget - Github || Demo

A web app for users to keep track of expenses & income.

- Whole website runs on Django.
- Store income and expenses in database
- Registers users to login

Eye CU - GitHub| Demo

A website for users to buy glasses and book appointments with an optician.

- Flask to store data about the user in a database.
- APIs to showcase the glasses to users from a camera.

TravelMauritius - GitHub| Demo

A guide for users to explore the Island of Mauritius

- LocalStorage to store encrypted user information client-side.
- APIs to demonstrate the weather and map(By region).

EXPERIENCE

CUSTOMER ONBOARDING REPRESENTATIVE

SYNAEGIS Co. LTD

Ebene, Mauritius 11/2018 - 04/2019

- The job consisted mainly of advising clients about investment opportunities worldwide.
- Assisted the team leader with assigning leads and troubleshooting issues.

SALESPERSON Rose-Hill, Mauritius **MEDIASPACE** 10/2016 - 01/2017 11/2017 - 01/2018

It consisted of selling a wide range of products to customers.

Helped manage its social media by keeping in touch with customers and advertising products.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, Python and Javascript program

Developers.Institute.Mauritius, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Pierrefonds. Mauritius 10/2021 - 01/2022

BCS Diploma in IT Sodnac, Mauritius 09/2020 - Present RUSHMORE BUSINESS SCHOOL

LANGUAGES

- English Fluent
- French Fluent
- Creole Fluent